RG 161:001, Connecticut State Police
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut State Police records
1919-2002
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Division of State Police
686.75 cubic feet
The Connecticut State Police (CSP) was founded in 1903 and is a division of the Connecticut Department of Public Safety which is responsible for traffic regulation and law enforcement across the state of Connecticut.
RG161_001
Multiple
Historical Note
The origins of the Connecticut State Police can be traced to the founding of the Law and Order League of Connecticut in 1884. The League was created by citizens who were dissatisfied with the inability, or unwillingness, of local police to enforce the laws of the State of Connecticut, particularly laws relating to intoxicating liquors. Over the years, League activities were extended to cover gambling and prostitution laws. In 1895 the League was incorporated, and in 1897 became quasi-official when the Governor was granted power to appoint four agents for the League. The League, however, was not effective due to its private status and the perception that they were meddling in law enforcement.
In 1903, Governor Abiram Chamberlain signed a legislative act that authorized the creation of the Connecticut State Police. Five state police commissioners were appointed to lay the groundwork for the first state police department with Thomas F. Egan named the agency's first superintendent. In 1905, the superintendent of the State Police also became the State Fire Marshall.
Over the years, the General Assembly has enacted many laws changing the organization, size, and duties of the State Police Department. In 1909 the State Police were given control over motion picture houses. In 1911 the Police were authorized to assist towns in enforcing motor vehicle laws and the State Police Superintendent was given the additional title of Superintendent of Weights and Measures. In 1919, the Superintendent was authorized to license amusement parks and to issue permits for concealed weapons. In 1920 the State Police were given joint control, with local fire marshals, over the licensing to manufacture, store, transport or sell explosives.
In 1921, six trooper barracks were established in rural areas, where the large majority of criminal investigations were being conducted. In 1927, the number of commissioners was reduced to one full-time salaried person appointed by the Governor. In 1931, the number of State Troopers was increased to 175 with 30 troopers assigned exclusively for highway patrol.
In 1939, Governor Raymond E. Baldwin appointed Edward J. Hickey as State Police Commissioner. Commissioner Hickey made several changes to the State Police including increasing the size of the department, using clearly marked police vehicles on state roads (to remind motorists of police presence) and updating the Bureau of Identification (the forerunner to the present day Forensics Lab). Hickey also established a State Police Training Academy, started gun-owner registrations, and used the nation's first motor vehicle radar (1946).
In 1947, the State Fire Marshall was required to establish a fire safety code. In 1951 the Commissioner of State Police was authorized to organize an emergency service, including necessary equipment and the creation of an auxiliary police force, to protect life and minority in case of fire, explosion, and floods. In 1963 the size of the State Police force increased to 500 men and 12 women; with a Criminal Intelligence Division created in 1967.
In 1977, a major reorganization of state government was started, saw the State Police Department made into one division of an overall Department of Safety, effective January 1, 1979. The Commissioner of Public Safety, who remained as administrative head and commanding officer of the State Police Division replaced the Commissioner of State Police. Also in 1977 a Statewide Narcotics Task Force was established within the State Police Division. And in 1986 a Legalized Gambling Investigation Unit was also established.
The Department of Emergency Services and Public Protection (DESPP) was established July 1, 2011 in an effort by the state to decrease the number of state agencies and reduce costs. DESPP is composed of six divisions: the Division of State Police, the Division of Statewide Emergency Telecommunications, the Division of Scientific Services, the Police Officer Standards and Training Council, the Commission on Fire Prevention and Control, and the Division of Emergency Management and Homeland Security.
See also the.
Scope and Content
Series 1. State Police Investigation Files, 1919-1998, contain records relating to specific cases under investigation by the State Police. Some of the landmark cases that are included in these files are: the Hartford Circus Fire, the Niles Street Hospital Fire, the Taborsky-Columbia Murder Case (Mad Dog Killers), and the State Leasing Probe. Also included are several files relating to other murder case investigations. The investigation files contain witness statements, investigating officer notes, background information, suspect files, photographs, and reports. Even after an official investigation has been closed, the investigation files may be updated with follow up reports, inquiries and records relating to subsequent re-examination of the original investigation, as is the case of the Hartford Circus Fire.
Series 2. Commissioner Files, 1980-1985, contain State Police Commissioner Donald J. Long's administrative files which include correspondence, State Police reports and publications, information sheets, notes, forms, and other materials relating to the daily duties of the State Police Commissioner.
Series 3. Connecticut State Police Troop A, 1923-1998; Series 4. Connecticut State Police Troop B, 1923-1998; Series 5. Connecticut State Police Troop C, 1922-1999; Series 6. Connecticut State Police Troop D, 1940-2002; Series 7. Connecticut State Police Troop E, 1924-1986; Series 8. Connecticut State Police Troop F, 1954-1999; Series 9. Connecticut State Police Troop G, 1939-1999; Series 10. Connecticut State Police Troop H, 1938-2000; Series 11. Connecticut State Police Troop I, 1935-1997; Series 12. Connecticut State Police Troop K, 1938-2002; Series 13. Connecticut State Police Troop L, 1942-1999, include case books and a variety of log books that document a wide range of incidents reported to the State Police, State Police procedures in recording this information, and attitudes of recording officers. Troops A and E records also include roll call books that document which officers were on duty on a particular day.
Series 14. Training Material, 1950-1951, contains a Connecticut State Auxiliary Training Course handout.
Arrangement
Series 1. State Police Investigation Files, 1919-1998, 293.75 cubic feet.
Investigation files, 1919-1963, Accession: 2000-020, 30 cubic feet.
Arranged chronologically by year and case number.
Investigation files, 1971, Accession: 2011-041, 4 cubic feet.
Arranged chronologically by case number.
Investigation files, 1940-1969, Accession: 2013-006, 57 cubic feet.
Investigation files, 1962-1975, Accession: 2013-017, 12 cubic feet.
Investigation files, 1970-1979, Accession: 2013-030, 109 cubic feet.
Investigation files, 1980-1982, Accession: 2013-041, 44 cubic feet.
Investigation files, 1976-1992, Accession: 2014-022, .5 cubic feet.
State Leasing case, 1970-1978, Accession: 1987-018, 29.25 cubic feet.
Nile Street Hospital file, 1945, Accession: 1987-018, .25 cubic feet.
Taborsky and Colombe murder case (Mad Dog killers), 1956-1957, Accession: 1987-018, 1 cubic foot.
Miscellaneous investigation files, 1956-1957, Accession: 1987-018, 2 cubic feet.
Charles Lindbergh Jr. kidnapping case, 1932, Accession: 1987-025, .25 cubic feet.
Hartford Circus Fire, 1941-1998, 4.5 cubic feet.
Accession: 1987-094, 4.25 cubic feet.
Accession: 2000-008, .25 cubic feet.
Report of Captain William L. Schatzman of investigation of the Southbury Training School, 1943, Accession: 2002-065, 1 folder.
Series 2. Commissioner Files, 1980-1985, 5.5 cubic feet.
Donald J. Long, 1980-1985, Accession: 1987-043, 5.5 cubic feet.
Arranged alphabetically by subject.
Series 3. Connecticut State Police Troop A, 1923-1998, 35 cubic feet.
Accession: 1989-031, 34 cubic feet.
Accession: 2013-028, 1 cubic foot.
Series 4. Connecticut State Police Troop B, 1923-1998, 33.5 cubic feet.
Accession: 2013-036, 33 cubic feet.
Accession: 2014-022, .5 cubic feet.
Series 5. Connecticut State Police Troop C, 1922-1999, Accession: 2013-026, 33 cubic feet.
Series 6. Connecticut State Police Troop D, 1940-2002, 31 cubic feet.
Accession: 2003-024, 28 cubic feet.
Accession: 2013-027, 3 cubic feet.
Series 7. Connecticut State Police Troop E, 1924-2000, 63 cubic feet.
Accession: 1989-030, 58 cubic feet.
Accession: 2013-039, 5 cubic feet.
Series 8. Connecticut State Police Troop F, 1954-1999, Accession: 2013-029, 24 cubic feet.
Series 9. Connecticut State Police Troop G, 1939-1999, Accession: 2013-038, 35 cubic feet.
Series 10. Connecticut State Police Troop H, 1938-2000, Accession: 2013-035, 38 cubic feet.
Series 11. Connecticut State Police Troop I, 1935-1997, Accession: 2013-034, 32 cubic feet.
Series 12. Connecticut State Police Troop K, 1938-2002, Accession: 2013-025, 31 cubic feet.
Series 13. Connecticut State Police Troop L, 1942-1999, 32 cubic feet.
Accession: 2012-001, 30 cubic feet.
Accession: 2013-037, 2 cubic feet.
Series 14. Training Material, 1950-1951, Accession: 2008-013, 1 folder.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Dept. of Emergency Services and Public Protection; Connecticut. Dept. of Public Safety; Connecticut. State Police Dept.; Connecticut. Division of State Police
Subjects:
Connecticut. State Police Dept. -- Records and correspondence; Police -- Connecticut; Connecticut. Dept. of Emergency Services and Public Protection -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. Division of State Police -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. Dept. of Public Safety -- Records and correspondence; Criminal investigation -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Attendance lists; Photographs; Correspondence; Logs (Records); Reports; Casebooks
Restrictions on Access
Series 1, State Police Investigation Files, 1919-1998, are RESTRICTED pending review unless otherwise indicated as files may contain confidential records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance. The investigation files for the Hartford Circus Fire are unrestricted.
Series 3, Connecticut State Police Troop A, 1923-1998, Accession: 1989-031, Accession: 2013-028; Series 4, Connecticut State Police Troop B, 1923-1998, Accession: 2013-036, Accession: 2014-022; Series 5, Connecticut State Police Troop C, 1922-1999, Accession: 2013-026; Series 6, Connecticut State Police Troop D, 1940-2002, Accession: 2003-024, Accession: 2013-027; Series 7, Connecticut State Police Troop E, 1924-2000, Accession: 1989-030, Accession: 2013-039; Series 8, Connecticut State Police Troop F, 1954-1999, Accession: 2013-029; Series 9, Connecticut State Police Troop G, 1939-1999, Accession: 2013-038; Series 10, Connecticut State Police Troop H, 1938-2000, Accession: 2013-035; Series 11, Connecticut State Police Troop I, 1935-1997, Accession: 2013-034; Series 12, Connecticut State Police Troop K, 1938-2002, Accession: 2013-025; and Series 13, Connecticut State Police Troop L, 1942-1999, Accession: 2012-001, Accession: 2013-037 are RESTRICTED per Connecticut General Statutes §54-142a.
Some of these records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
In 1987 the State Police transferred its investigation files for five cases: the Charles Lindbergh Jr. kidnapping, the Hartford Circus Fire, the Niles Street Hospital Fire, the Taborsky-Columbia Murder Case (Mad Dog Killers), and the State Leasing Probe. They also transferred the administrative files of Commissioner Donald Long. The State Police transferred additional information regarding the Hartford Circus Fire in 1999. Additional investigation files were transferred between 1999 and 2013. In 1989 the State Archives received case books, 1930-1979 and log books, 1923-1980 of Troop A of the State Police. Arrest log books, 1993-1998 of Troop A were transferred on January 31, 2013. Troop B books, 1923-1998 were transferred on March 5, 2013 and assignment of complaints log books were transferred on November 8, 2013. Troop C books, 1922-1999 were transferred on January 30, 2013. Troop D log books,1940-1995 in accession 2003-024 were transferred in 2003. Troop D case books and arrest log books in accession 2013-027 were transferred on January 30, 2013. Troop E case books, 1951-1978 and log books, 1924-1986 were also transferred in 1989. Troop E case books, 1985-2000 in accession 2013-039 were transferred on March 19, 2013. Troop F books, 1954-1999 were transferred on February 6, 2013. Troop G books, 1939-1999 were transferred on March 7, 2013. Troop H books, 1938-2000 were transferred on February 26, 2013. Troop I books, 1935-1997 were transferred on February 21, 2013. Troop K books, 1938-2002 were transferred on January 18, 2013. Troop L books, 1942-1999 in accession 2012-001 were transferred on July 6, 2011. Troop L case books, 1945-1984 in accession 2013-037 were transferred on March 5, 2013. Connecticut State Police auxiliary training course handout was transferred in 2008.
Container List
- Series 1. State Police Investigation Files, 1919-1998; 293.75 cubic feet
  The files in this series are RESTRICTED pending review unless otherwise indicated.
  - Investigation files, 1919-1963; 2000-020; 30 cubic feet
    Arranged chronologically by year and case number.
    - 240 - B-3624, 1919-1924 (Box 1)
    - B-3931 - E-1064, 1924-1927 (Box 2)
    - E-1541 - F-7904, 1927-1928 (Box 3)
    - F-8033 - G-950, 1928-1929 (Box 4)
    - G-3398 - H-12310, 1929-1932 (Box 5)
    - I-2247 - J-13471, 1930-1932 (Box 6)
    - K-321 - L-9713, 1932-1934 (Box 7)
    - L-10652 - N-1592, 1934-1936 (Box 8)
    - N-2843 - R-454, 1935-1939 (Box 9)
    - 4876 - 34529, 1938-1940 (Box 10)
    - 35454 - A-1027-U, 1940-1942 (Box 11)
    - L-1-X - E-536-X, 1942-1943 (Box 12)
    - I-74-Y - C-494-Y, 1943-1944 (Box 13)
    - D-563-Y - F-772-Y, 1943-1944 (Box 14)
    - A-886-Y - H107-A, 1943-1946 (Box 15)
    - L-407-A - C-757-B, 1946-1947 (Box 16)
    - S-128-B, 1946-1947 (Box 17)
    - S-128-B - E-808-B, 1946-1947 (Box 18)
    - I-894-B - E-718-C, 1947-1948 (Box 19)
    - D-1276-C - I-704-G, 1948-1951 (Box 20)
    - I-435-F, 1950 October 8 (Box 21)
    - C-776-G - G-1246-H, 1952-1953 (Box 22)
    - G-1246-H, 1953 (Box 23)
    - H-1250-H - G-913-K, 1953-1955 (Box 24)
    - A-769-K - H-1100-L, 1955-1956 (Box 25)
    - K-150-O - DH-101-S, 1958-1961 (Box 26)
    - E-801-S - A-1047-UU, 1961-1963 (Box 27)
    - A-860-P, 1959 November 18 (Box 28)
    - 1943, 1946, 1956 (Box 29)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 30)
  - Investigation files, 1971; 2011-041; 4 cubic feet
    Arranged by case number. Case number is preceded by Troop letter and 71. For example K-71-0026.
    - 0026 - 0968 (Box 1)
    - 0973 - 1920 (Box 2)
    - 1926 - 3943 (Box 3)
    - Additional folders for cases Y-71-120, Y-71-147, Y-71-178, Y-71-180 (Box 4)
  - Investigation files, 1940-1969; 2013-006; 57 cubic feet
    - 1940-1941, 1955 (Box 1)
    - 1956 (Box 2)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 3)
    - 1959 (Box 4)
    - 1960 August-1963 (Box 5)
    - 1963 September-October (Box 6)
    - 1963 November-December (Box 7)
    - 1964 January-March (Box 8)
    - 1964 January-June (Box 9)
    - 1964 March-July (Box 10)
    - 1964 July-September (Box 11)
    - 1964 September-November (Box 12)
    - 1964 November-1965 July, 1967 February (Box 13)
    - 1964 July-1965 May (Box 14)
    - 1965 January-August (Box 15)
    - 1965 July-October, 1966 March (Box 16)
    - 1965 August-1966 January (Box 17)
    - 1965 October-1966 May (Box 18)
    - 1965 December-1966 June (Box 19)
    - 1966 January-June (Box 20)
    - 1966 April-June (Box 21)
    - 1968 January-December (Box 22)
    - 1968 February-July (Box 23)
    - 1968 March-September (Box 24)
    - 1968 June-December (Box 25)
    - 1968 August-December (Box 26)
    - 1968 June, September-December (Box 27)
    - 1968 November-December (Box 28)
    - Manwaring murder, E-1595-ZZ, 1966 December 1966; 2 boxes (Box 29A-29B)
    - Randall murder, C-2164-XX, 1965 June 25; 2 boxes (Box 30A-30B)
    - 1958-1963 (Box 31)
    - 1964 May-June, November-December (Box 32)
    - 1965 January-March (Box 33)
    - 1965 April-May (Box 34)
    - 1965 June-July (Box 35)
    - 1966 July-August (Box 36)
    - 1966 September (Box 37)
    - 1966 October (Box 38)
    - 1966 November-December (Box 39)
    - 1967 January (Box 40)
    - 1967 February (Box 41)
    - 1967 March-April (Box 42)
    - 1967 May-June (Box 43)
    - 1967 July-August (Box 44)
    - 1967 September-October (Box 45)
    - Morgan murder, E-67-910, 1967 October 9 (Box 45A)
    - 1967 November-December (Box 46)
    - Beaupre murder, Y-67-0063, 1967 December 18 (Box 46A)
    - 1969 February-March (Box 47)
    - 1969 April-May (Box 48)
    - 1969 June (Box 49)
    - 1969 July-August (Box 50)
    - 1968 October, 1969 September-October (Box 51)
    - 1969 November-December (Box 52)
    - 1967 May-October (Box 53)
  - Investigation files, 1962-1975; 2013-017; 12 cubic feet
    - Shelton Sponge Rubber Plant fire, Y-75-44, 1975 (Box 1-10)
    - F-797-T, 1962 (Box 11)
    - G-69-646, 1969 (Box 11)
    - E-69-972, 1969 (Box 11)
    - DH-114-YY, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Investigation files, 1970-1979; 2013-030; 109 cubic feet
    - 1970 (Box 1-2)
    - 1971 (Box 3)
    - 1972 (Box 4-14)
    - 1973 (Box 15-23)
    - 1974 (Box 24-42)
    - 1975 (Box 43-49)
    - 1976 (Box 50-60)
    - 1977 (Box 61-78)
    - 1978 (Box 79-91)
    - 1979 (Box 92-109)
  - Investigation files, 1980-1982; 2013-041; 44 cubic feet
    - 1980 (Box 1-16)
    - 1981 (Box 17-29)
    - 1982 (Box 30-44)
  - Investigation files, 1976-1992; 2014-022; .5 cubic feet
    - Jewett City investigation files (Box 1)
  - State Leasing case, 1970-1978; 1987-018; 29.25 cubic feet
    - Notes on Larry Stern (Box 1)
    - Correspondence on Thomas Meskill (Box 1)
    - List of Real Estate Brokers (Box 1)
    - File on DeLorenzo (Box 1)
    - Chronology of Phoenix Building lease (Box 1)
    - Roger Ladd file (Box 1)
    - Allan Schaefer file (Box 1)
    - Larry Stern file (Box 1)
    - T. DeLorenzo checking account file (Box 1)
    - CSP report, 1978 October 12 (Box 1)
    - Testimony of Governor Meskill (Box 1)
    - Info on Greater Hartford Community College (Box 1)
    - Building permits for Phoenix lease (Box 1)
    - CSP case Y-76-0041-C larceny (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 2)
    - File on Public Works audit of Phoenix Building (Box 2)
    - Phoenix chronology chart (Box 2)
    - Work sheet: analysis of cancelled checks, account of DeLorenzo for Mayor (Box 2)
    - DOT lease Y-76-0063-C (Box 3)
    - Possessed property receipt (Box 3)
    - Possessed property report on Davis and Nye purchase order (Box 3)
    - Davis and Nye purchase order (Box 3)
    - State Housing Commission Report (Box 3)
    - Middlesex Community College sites selection study (Box 3)
    - Documents re: purchase of equipment MXCC (Box 3)
    - Affidavit of John Marsella (Box 3)
    - Notes from O'Marra to McCann (Box 3)
    - Notes from Roscoe to Dino Nucci (Box 3)
    - Dr. K. Summer file (Box 3)
    - Bradley Biggs file (Box 4)
    - Roger Heinz file (Box 4)
    - DeMatteo Construction file (Box 4)
    - Morris Stulin file (Box 4)
    - William Mack file (Box 4)
    - Paul Manaford file (Box 4)
    - MXCC equipment listings and cost file (Box 4)
    - B. Sherwill file (Box 4)
    - B. Sherwill file (Box 4)
    - Lease material bonus and trustee sales records (Box 4)
    - Middlesex equipment agency listing (Box 4)
    - Middlesex master file (Box 4)
    - Eastern Connecticut College Dial access (Box 5)
    - Labor Department lease - Norwich (Box 5)
    - Report of Sub-Committee on Appropriations (Box 5)
    - Preliminary report: Review of leasing probe materials (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 5)
    - Affidavit of Charles Cavanna (Box 5)
    - Correspondence - leasing probe (Box 5)
    - Constitution Bank and Trust to Zaniewski, 1976 August 16 (Box 5)
    - Option agreement - Constitution Bank (Box 5)
    - Affidavit of James Shay and James Carey (Box 5)
    - Chester Zaniewski file (Box 5)
    - CFU Management Corp (Box 6)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 6)
    - Real estate listings (Box 6)
    - Lease proposal outline (Box 6)
    - Bond for deed $3,485,000.00 (Box 6)
    - Bond for deed $3,570,000.00 (Box 6)
    - Public Works file (Box 6)
    - Attorney Roscoe file (Box 6)
    - Appraisal - Richard Barry (Box 6)
    - Appraisal - Dow and Condon (Box 6)
    - Richard Rockwell file (Box 7)
    - CSP reports (Box 7)
    - Affidavit of Zaniewski (Box 7)
    - Union Commerce Bank file (Box 7)
    - Bond for Deed 1 Myrtle Street (Box 7)
    - Certified resolution CFU Management Corp. (Box 7)
    - Sloate Square brochure (Box 7)
    - Rockwell correspondence re: Roscoe (Box 7)
    - Weinerman correspondence to Jackson, 1977 May 25 (Box 7)
    - McTeague correspondence (Box 7)
    - Allan Schaefer file (Box 7)
    - Rough draft, 1977 August 25 (Box 7)
    - Capitol Center Property Acquisition file, cassettes (Box 7)
    - Attorney Roscoe file (Box 7)
    - Jackson memoranda to Weinerman, 1977 May 16 (Box 7)
    - Barone letter to Feldman, 1976 August 5 (Box 7)
    - Brunette letter to McKinnon, 1978 March 2 (Box 7)
    - Weinerman letter to Schaefer, 1976 September 9 (Box 7)
    - Request for purchase proposals (Box 7)
    - Rough draft of history of 1 Myrtle Street (Box 7)
    - Bronetti letter to McKinnon, 1978 March 2 (Box 7)
    - Information itemized for review of property review board (Box 7)
    - Hurwitz letter to Community Public Works, 1977 September 29 (Box 7)
    - Barone letter to Zaniewski, 1976 September 13 (Box 7)
    - Bauer letter to Schaefer, 1977 October 20 (Box 7)
    - Quarrier letter to Rockwell, 1976 August 3 (Box 7)
    - Complaint of Dr. G. Gunther, 1978 March 17 (Box 7)
    - Zaniewski letter to Gionfriddo, 1977 September 18 (Box 7)
    - Burnette letter to Zaniewski, 1978 February 21 (Box 7)
    - LaPorte letter to Zaniewski, 1975 December 9 (Box 7)
    - Barone letter to Baldwin, 1975 August 25 (Box 7)
    - Zaniewski letter to Brunette, 1978 April 12 (Box 7)
    - Frank Manaford file (Box 8)
    - CSP Report Y-76-0008 (Box 8)
    - Bradley Biggs file (Box 8)
    - Structural file (Box 8)
    - DeMatteo Construction file (Box 8)
    - Change order requests (Box 9)
    - DOT weight unit prices (Box 9)
    - Material on change order requests (Box 9)
    - Paul Manaford file (Box 9)
    - Delco Construction Company (Box 9)
    - Biggs International Development Corp. (Box 9)
    - Olson and Miller Co. (Box 9)
    - New Haven testing labs (Box 9)
    - DeMatteo Construction Corp. (Box 9)
    - Federal funds for HE-2 (Box 9)
    - Final report of Legislative Committee (Box 9)
    - CM contract, HE-2 (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous contract work, HE-2 (Box 9)
    - DeMatteo Construction, materials HE-2 (Box 9)
    - Stein, Sedzck and Ames file (Box 9)
    - Affidavit of Dino Nucci (Box 9)
    - Bob Leasing Case (Box 10)
    - Site development CNVR, HE-2 (Box 10)
    - Changes order, structural/gravel (Box 10)
    - HE-2 expenditures (Box 10)
    - Manaford and MBI Loans exchange (Box 10)
    - Affidavit of Henry Margolis (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 10)
    - Mattatuck Community College files (Box 10)
    - Henry Margolis file (Box 11)
    - Labor Department reports (Box 11)
    - Construction manager analysis (Box 11)
    - Affidavit of James B. White (Box 11)
    - Audio tapes of State Police interviews (Box 12)